[
  { "question": "cabbage (n)\n/ˈkæb.ɪdʒ/", "answer": "bắp cải" },
  { "question": "carrot (n)\n/ˈkær.ət/", "answer": "cà rốt" },
  { "question": "potato (n)\n/pəˈteɪ.t̬oʊ/", "answer": "khoai tây" },
  { "question": "sweet potato (n)\n/ˌswiːt pəˈteɪ.t̬oʊ/", "answer": "khoai lang" },
  { "question": "tomato (n)\n/təˈmeɪ.t̬oʊ/", "answer": "cà chua" },
  { "question": "cucumber (n)\n/ˈkjuː.kʌm.bɚ/", "answer": "dưa chuột" },
  { "question": "pumpkin (n)\n/ˈpʌmp.kɪn/", "answer": "bí ngô" },
  { "question": "zucchini (n)\n/zuːˈkiː.ni/", "answer": "bí xanh (bí ngòi)" },
  { "question": "onion (n)\n/ˈʌn.jən/", "answer": "hành tây" },
  { "question": "garlic (n)\n/ˈɡɑːr.lɪk/", "answer": "tỏi" },
  { "question": "ginger (n)\n/ˈdʒɪn.dʒɚ/", "answer": "gừng" },
  { "question": "radish (n)\n/ˈræd.ɪʃ/", "answer": "củ cải" },
  { "question": "turnip (n)\n/ˈtɝː.nɪp/", "answer": "củ cải tròn" },
  { "question": "beetroot (n)\n/ˈbiːt.ruːt/", "answer": "củ dền" },
  { "question": "pea (n)\n/piː/", "answer": "đậu Hà Lan" },
  { "question": "green bean (n)\n/ˌɡriːn ˈbiːn/", "answer": "đậu cô ve" },
  { "question": "soybean (n)\n/ˈsɔɪ.biːn/", "answer": "đậu nành" },
  { "question": "corn (n)\n/kɔːrn/", "answer": "ngô, bắp" },
  { "question": "cauliflower (n)\n/ˈkɑː.lɪ.flaʊ.ɚ/", "answer": "súp lơ" },
  { "question": "broccoli (n)\n/ˈbrɑː.kəl.i/", "answer": "bông cải xanh" },
  { "question": "eggplant (n)\n/ˈeɡ.plænt/", "answer": "cà tím" },
  { "question": "celery (n)\n/ˈsel.ɚ.i/", "answer": "cần tây" },
  { "question": "leek (n)\n/liːk/", "answer": "tỏi tây" },
  { "question": "lettuce (n)\n/ˈlet̬.ɪs/", "answer": "rau diếp" },
  { "question": "mushroom (n)\n/ˈmʌʃ.ruːm/", "answer": "nấm" },
  { "question": "chili (pepper) (n)\n/ˈtʃɪl.i ˌpep.ɚ/", "answer": "ớt cay" },
  { "question": "bell pepper (n)\n/ˈbel ˌpep.ɚ/", "answer": "ớt chuông" },
  { "question": "spinach (n)\n/ˈspɪn.ɪtʃ/", "answer": "rau chân vịt (bina)" },
  { "question": "herb (n)\n/hɝːb/", "answer": "rau thơm (nói chung)" }
]
